newsgab.com 2009-05-21

# Newsgab » Privacy Policy

**Newsgab respects your privacy**

Newsgab respects your privacy. Any personal information you give us is held with the utmost care and security, according to the guidelines set forth in the UK Data Protection Acts of 1998, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. We will not sell or disclose any information that identifies you to a third party without your approval. Information is stored at our US data processing centre. Please continue to read our privacy policy for more details.

**Your personal information**

Newsgab will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. For example, if you would like to register on our site to use our forums or contribute an article then we ask for your e-mail address.

If you register, you can also sign up to receive our newsletter which may contain information from Newsgab and other qualified companies. These qualified suppliers are pre-screened organisations or companies whose products or services we believe are of interest to you. If you sign up to receive the offers but later decide you don’t want them, then you can easily unsubscribe via your member control panel. 

Obviously we will not give your email address to these companies unless we obtain your consent.

Our site has public areas such as our forums. Please remember that any information you share in these areas becomes public, so you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

If you post comments about Newsgab on our site, there’s a chance we may publish them for editorial purposes or in promotional advertising and/or marketing materials (especially if you say nice things about us). However, anything we do use will not identify you as an individual.

**Cookies**

Newsgab uses a feature of your Internet Web browser called a “cookie” to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer’s hard drive. Newsgab creates and then uses these cookie files to track your clicks as you go through the Newsgab Web site. Newsgab only uses cookies to tell us whether you have visited Newsgab previously, and to help us determine whether you came to Newsgab from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. Cookies can also be used to help to save and retrieve passwords used on the Newsgab site and information other preferences, saving you from having to re-enter this information upon every visit to the Newsgab Web site. Newsgab does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless you knowingly and willingly provided such information.

**Online surveys and contests**

Sometimes we conduct user surveys to improve our site for you. We may share aggregate, or summary, anonymous information about our users with partners or other third parties. For example, we might disclose that a certain percentage of our users are male. But we will not sell or share any information at the individual user level. 

Reviewing and changing your personal profile

Once you register, you will be able to review and change your personal profile at any time.
